

# **ARIF BUDI SURYONO**

# PRIVATE PROFILE

S1 Informatics Engineering graduate, has more than 3 years of experience operating CNC machines. Hard worker, communicative, and likes things that add knowledge. Able to work under pressure, and able to work in a team or individually.

## **EDUCATION**

2011-2014

#### **SMK Sakti Gemolong**

• Mechanical Engineering

2021

### **Duta Bangsa University**

• S1 Informatics Engineering

## SKILL

- Team work
- Communication
- Focus in the long term

## **EXPERIENCE**

### 2014-2016 | PT. Musashi Autopart

- Carry out the production process of car gear makers with machines
- Making production reports
- Develop standard operating procedures for the production process

#### 2017-2018 | CV. Ribka Furniture

- Carry out the production process
- · Coloring wood furniture
- Doing shipping goods packing

## 2019-2021 | PT. Mmf Metal Fabrication

- Carry out the production process of making drill bits
- Making production reports
- Develop standard operating procedures for the production process

## HOBBY —

Futsal sport